Hello friends, to activate the ICC Bank mobile
application, you must have a
registered SIM card in your mobile
and an ATM card. Only then will you be
able to use this application.
To download this application, you have to
go to Play Store and type 'I am
mobile' and from here you will download this application.
After the download is complete, you will see that the 'Activate Now' button will be
displayed here. By clicking on this option, you will verify
this application through your registered SIM.
After the verification is complete, you will see that the option to generate a PIN will be displayed on the next page
from where you will be
able to generate the PIN for this mobile application. To generate this PIN code, you will
see that at the top you have to generate a four-digit
PIN and after that, after
confirming below, you have to click on the submit button.
From here, see that our
PAN has been successfully generated. Now
on the next page, we have to
complete our authentication through the ATM card. There is
some ABCD code given on the back of our ATM card.
We have to enter this number here and click on the activate button.  If you
want to do it then friends,
you can activate the mobile application by following this simple process.
If
you liked this video friends, then
like this video and subscribe to our channel
and also press the bell button so
that
you can see our upcoming video first. So friends, that's all for today,
we will meet in the next video. Till then,
thank you, Jai Hind.